Guide to the Allen Ginsberg film and video archive, 1983 - 1996
Department of Special Collections
- I Believe: Allen Ginsberg. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Allen Ginsberg reading poetry.
    Time in: 4:00:44 Time out: 4:01:09 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "When I sit I see..."
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 4:01:25 Time out: 4:07:18 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg talks about his relationship with his parents, his "homosexual conditioning," auditory hallucinations of Blake's poetry and the search for his and America's souls.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 4:09:14 Time out: 4:19:50 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses the soul, the ego, death, his non-grasping love for Peter Orlovsky and Buddhism vs. Christianity.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 4:21:51 Time out: 4:26:39 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg remarks on observing one's thoughts, the humor in his early poetry, the early Beats and the word "Beat," and the claim that he is a kind of prophet.
  - Allen Ginsberg reading a short poem.
    Time in: 4:22:16 Time out: 4:22:41 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Wind makes sound..." Out: "... it's the wind talking."
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 4:27:47 Time out: 4:29:30 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg commenting on his work being used as a teaching tool. Ginsberg then closes the show by singing a mantra.
- Beyond Self, Beyond War. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:48:45 Total Time: 48m 45s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  By John Miglietta, 1986. Includes footage from John Miglietta's 1984 interview (see Tape 12).
  - Allen Ginsberg introduced.
    Time in: 0:02:40 Time out: 0:02:50 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg introduced as part of this program.
  - Footage of Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:04:15 Time out: 0:04:20 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg is shown sitting in the audience.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:08:40 Time out: 0:11:20 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg voices his anger and rage over US involvement in worldwide covert operations.
  - Footage of Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:12:15 Time out: 0:12:20 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg is shown in the audience.
  - Footage of Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:19:30 Time out: 0:19:40 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg participates in a walking meditation.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:23:45 Time out: 0:25:20 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg tells about conflicts he had with his father.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:26:40 Time out: 0:27:00 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg comments on women in Buddhism.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:28:30 Time out: 0:29:00 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:29:50 Time out: 0:33:10 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg explains his involvement with the protest at Rocky Flats.
  - Footage of Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:43:20 Time out: 0:43:25 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    We see Ginsberg taking part in a tea ceremony.
  - Footage of Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:47:20 Time out: 0:47:50 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg is shown as he walks away near the end of the film.
- Poets on Videotape: Writer's Forum #1. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:58:52 Total Time: 58m 52s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Television program featuring an in-depth conversation with Allen Ginsberg, 1970.
  - Poets on Videotape: Writer's Forum #2.
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:58:51 Total Time: 58m 51s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A second visit with Allen Ginsberg, 1973.
- Breathing Together: Revolution of the Electric Family. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:24:29 Total Time: 24m 29s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A film by Morley Markson, filmed mostly in 1968-69, released in 1971.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Peter Orlovsky.
    Time in: 0:01:05 Time out: 0:02:40 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Orlovsky on their communal farm, bring in goats and calves for the night.
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:02:50 Time out: 0:05:44 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads a section of "Howl", both on camera and over images of subways.
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:05:51 Time out: 0:08:59 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Hare Krishna's chant at the Washington Monument over images of the Chicago 1968 protest. Abbie Hoffman talks about revolution on the phone.
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:09:00 Time out: 0:13:04 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings "Jessore Road" and plays the harmonium.
  - Demonstrators.
    Time in: 0:13:05 Time out: 0:13:49 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Chicago anti-war protest, 1968.
  - Timothy Leary, John Lennon, Yoko Ono.
    Time in: 0:13:50 Time out: 0:15:21 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Interview with Leary at a flower power demonstration, 1968. Demonstrators chant, "Give Peace a Chance" along with John Lennon and Yoko Ono.
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:15:24 Time out: 0:17:53 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg, in 1968, comments on the ecology disaster karma that we are developing.
  - Demonstration.
    Time in: 0:17:54 Time out: 0:19:04 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Dancing and police brutality in the streets.
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:19:05 Time out: 0:19:53 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg comments on every culture's need for sacred music and sacred substances.
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:19:54 Time out: 0:21:14 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses alternate strategies other than force that could have defeated Hitler.
  - Final credits of the movie.
    Time in: 0:22:00 Time out: 0:24:29 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The credits roll over Allen chanting "Ohm" on camera.
- Allen and Student; Rocky Flats. (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:38:00 Total Time: 27m 0s Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  This is a transfer from 16mm work print film. See detailed descriptions below.
  - Allen and Student, 1984.
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:10:00 Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen teaches a student about poetry on the grass outside of his Bluff St. house in Boulder.
  - Rocky Flats, 1985.
    Time in: 0:21:00 Time out: 0:38:00 Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Documentation of an attempted encirclement of the nuclear trigger factory near Boulder by 10,000 people. Ginsberg and other Naropa faculty and students are a part of this demonstration.
- Carl Solomon Interview; Allen Signing Books; Ginsberg Photo Show. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Time in: 0:00:54 Time out: 0:17:54 Total Time: 17m 54s Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Carl Solomon Interview.
    Time in: 0:00:54 Time out: 0:05:53 Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    New York City, 1985. Better quality transfer on Tape 74.
  - Allen Signing Books.
    Time in: 0:05:54 Time out: 0:12:46 Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg signs his first hard cover poetry book in 1985 at the Holly Solomon Gallery in New York City.
  - People at Photo Show.
    Time in: 0:12:47 Time out: 0:17:54 Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Shots of a large crowd of people studying Ginsberg's first full photo exhibit at the Holly Solomon Gallery, 1985.
- Ginsberg Coffee House Poetry Reading; Ginsberg and Gregory Corso. (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:53:00 Total Time: 53m 0s Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Ginsberg Coffee House Poetry Reading.
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:16:00 Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads poetry in a typical coffee house setting, New York City, 1985.
  - Gregory Corso and Allen Ginsberg conversing, late 1980's.
    Time in: 0:16:00 Time out: 0:53:00 Source: 16mm Film Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Corso and Ginsberg converse with each other on a Boulder back porch.
- What Happened to Kerouac?, Part I. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:57:05 Total Time: 57m 05s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  This film, by Richard Lerner, 1985, is one of the two best-known documentaries on the life of Jack Kerouac. The editor of this film also edited The Life and Times of Allen Ginsberg.
  - Ginsberg talking about 1969 Firing Line.
    Time in: 0:08:19 Time out: 0:08:53 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg states that Kerouac was incredibly drunk and bored while on the show.
  - Herbert Huncke and Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:11:17 Time out: 0:12:25 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Huncke and Ginsberg talk about when they first met Kerouac and their impressions of him.
  - Gregory Corso interview.
    Time in: 0:22:20 Time out: 0:22:46 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Corso describes the first time Ginsberg, Kerouac and Burroughs met.
  - Herbert Huncke and Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:23:48 Time out: 0:25:53 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Huncke and Ginsberg discuss Times Square and the New York City scene in the 1940's.
  - Anne Charters interview.
    Time in: 0:29:05 Time out: 0:30:25 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ann Charters talks about the first reading of "Howl" and Kerouac at that reading, which he later described in The Dharma Bums.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Neal Cassady in the basement of City Lights bookstore, San Francisco.
    Time in: 0:38:19 Time out: 0:42:23 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Beautiful black and white transfer of famous City Lights footage. There is discussion about who is really in charge of the US -- the military or the elected government.
- What Happened to Kerouac?, Part II. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:40:19 Total Time: 40m 19s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  This film, by Richard Lerner, 1985, is one of the two best known documentaries on the life of Jack Kerouac. The editor of this film also edited The Life and Times of Allen Ginsberg.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:14:09 Time out: 0:15:06 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen comments on New York City intellectuals and their sentiments against Kerouac's writings.
  - Ann Charters interview.
    Time in: 0:18:31 Time out: 0:19:54 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ann Charters describes the relationships between Kerouac, Burroughs, Corso and Ginsberg and why those relationships couldn't last as they grew older.
  - Huncke and Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:21:16 Time out: 0:22:54 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Huncke and Ginsberg discuss the relationship between Kerouac and his mother.
  - Huncke and Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:32:01 Time out: 0:34:12 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg describes his last visit to Kerouac. He remarks about Kerouac's grief, joy and suffering, and alcoholic demise the last 10 years of his life.
- Ginsberg Family 8mm Footage: Hannah Litsky Home Movies. (Box 6, Folder 51)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:12:54 Total Time: 12m 54s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  1938: black and white footage. 1946: color footage. All silent.
  - Ginsberg family, black and white. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:02:20 Time out: 0.02.56 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen with brother, Eugene, and father, Louis.
  - Ginsberg family, black and white. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:02:59 Time out: 0:03:24 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Naomi, Allen's mother, alone and with Allen, Eugene and Louis.
  - Ginsberg family, black and white. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:03:33 Time out: 0:03:47 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen and Eugene.
  - Allen Ginsberg, black and white. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:03:54 Time out: 0:04:03 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen with some of his friends.
  - Ginsberg family, black and white. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0.05.25 Time out: 0:05:37 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Ginsberg family, color. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:07:52 Time out: 0:08:17 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen, Eugene and Louis.
  - Ginsberg family, color. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:10:33 Time out: 0:10:38 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen with a baby.
  - Ginsberg family, color. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:10:55 Time out: 0:11:20 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen and his family play in the water at the beach.
  - Allen Ginsberg, color. (Folder 51)
    Time in: 0:12:12 Time out: 0:12:24 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen with beach ball.
- The Simpsons: "Bart vs. Thanksgiving". (Box 6, Folder 52)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:23:20 Total Time: 23m 20s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Episode #7F07 of The Simpsons, satirical cartoon television series, November, 22, 1990.
  - Lisa Simpson, cartoon character. (Folder 52)
    Time in: 0:13:30 Time out: 0:13:46 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Lisa Simpson writes her version of "Howl".
  - Lisa Simpson, cartoon character. (Folder 52)
    Time in: 0:16:27 Time out: 0:16:42 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Lisa Simpson attempts to read her version of "Howl", but is interrupted.
- 1968 Chicago Democratic Convention Riot Footage. (Box 6, Folder 53)
  Time in: 15:34:41 Time out: 15:40:01 Total Time: 5m 20s Source: 3/4" Master with visible Time Code Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master with visible Time Code
  Portions of a film made by the University of Illinois. This is from a 3/4" Window Dub Master with visible Time Code numbers superimposed on the image of all formats.
  - Chicago 1968 Demonstration. (Folder 53)
    Time in: 15:34:41 Time out: 15:37:45 Source: 3/4" Master with visible Time Code Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master with visible Time Code
    Riot footage from Chicago Democratic Convention, including tear gas, police violence. The shots take place during the day and the night.
  - Allen Ginsberg chanting. (Folder 53)
    Time in: 15:37:46 Time out: 15:40:01 Source: 3/4" Master with visible Time Code Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master with visible Time Code
    Ginsberg chants in Lincoln Park in Chicago, calming the crowd at the Democratic Convention, 1968.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part I. (Box 6, Folder 54)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:18:29 Total Time: 18m 29s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, 1986. This interview was filmed in the library of a mansion on Mapleton Hill. Allen talks about his life to that point.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part II. (Box 6, Folder 55)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:21:53 Total Time: 21m 53s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, 1986. Interview continued.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part III. (Box 6, Folder 56)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:18:20 Total Time: 18m 20s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part IV. (Box 6, Folder 57)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:18:17 Total Time: 18m 17s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part V. (Box 6, Folder 58)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:17:20 Total Time: 17m 20s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part VI. (Box 6, Folder 59)
  Time in: 6:01:03 Time out: 6:18:42 Total Time: 17m 39s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, 1986. Continuing from the preceding interview session, Ginsberg reads some of his poetry.
  - "A Meaningless Institution". (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:01:03 Time out: 6.01.39 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "A Meaningless Institution" Out: "... in search of a toilet."
  - "Psalm I". (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:02:00 Time out: 6:02:58 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Psalm I ..." Out: "... the Dove descends."
  - "My Alba". (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:03:24 Time out: 6:04:15 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Now that I've wasted..." Out: "... alarm clock is ringing."
  - "Siesta In Xbalba and Return to the States" (Abridged). (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:05:55 Time out: 6:07:14 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "After 15 hrs..." Out: "... dusk submission."
  - "On Burroughs' Work". (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:07:46 Time out: 6:08:14 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "On Burroughs' Work..." Out: "... hide the madness."
  - "Love Poem on Theme by Whitman" (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:08:44 Time out: 6:10:13 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Love Poem..." Out: "... in the silence."
  - "Malest Cornifici Tuo Catullo". (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:10:54 Time out: 6:11:20 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "I'm happy, Kerouac..." Out: "... it's like Heaven."
  - "A Strange New Cottage in Berkeley". (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:11:39 Time out: 6:12:29 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "A strange new cottage..." Out: "... dry, lovelorn tongue."
  - "Europe! Europe!" (Abridged). (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:12:53 Time out: 6:14:49 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Europe! Europe!" Out: "... empty tombs."
  - "First Party at Ken Kesey's with Hell's Angels" Take 1. (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:16:20 Time out: 6:17:31 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "First Party..." Out: "... in the leaves."
  - "First Party at Ken Kesey's with Hell's Angels" Take 2. (Folder 59)
    Time in: 6:17:38 Time out: 6:18:42 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part VII. (Box 6, Folder 60)
  Time in: 7:00:00 Time out: 7.16.22 Total Time: 16m 22s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, 1986. A series of private readings of Ginsberg's poetry by Ginsberg.
  - "Going to Chicago" (Abridged). (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:01:32 Time out: 7:02:32 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "The lake blue..." Out: "... Metal Microphone."
  - "Grant Park: August 28, 1968". (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:02:54 Time out: 7:03:38 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Green air..." Out: "... garden of Eden?"
  - "Rain-wet asphalt heat, garbage curbed cans". (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:04:57 Time out: 7:07:06 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "Memory Gardens" (Abridged). (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:07:17 Time out: 7:08:26 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Northport in the trees...." Out: "... drunken dumbshow."
  - "Returning to the Country for a Brief Visit" (Abridged). (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:08:53 Time out: 7:09:54 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Returning to the Country...." Out: "... in dark Rain."
  - "Drive All Blames into One". (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:10:33 Time out: 7:11:15 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Drive All Blames..." Out: "... had a hardon."
  - "Brooklyn College Brain". (Folder 60)
    Time in: 7:11:33 Time out: 7:12:39 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Brooklyn College Brain..." Out: "... in the Birdroom."